Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Employee Service Awards Group Shot and EMPO individual, 2014- (Box-folder 44-311)
- Homecoming: Wildfire, Alumni Awards Dinner, Color Run, Football, 2014- (Box-folder 44-312)
- ML CTR Student (COB) Tess Goulet, 2005- (Box-folder 45-1)
- Media Services Staff, 2005- (Box-folder 45-2)
- Billboard P.S. Finals, Science Trumpet Bus, 2005- (Box-folder 45-3)
- Dan Jack, Natalie Lefkowitz, Leanne Todd, 2005- (Box-folder 45-4)
- Kent Johnson, Morning Side Academy, 2005- (Box-folder 45-5)
- Kristl Miller Shots Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-6)
- Kristl Miller Shots Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-7)
- Development Staff Jen Gray, Brad melton, Connie Roberts, Libby Street Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-8)
- Mark Trahant, 2005- (Box-folder 45-9)
- Distinguished Professors, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 45-10)
- Miscellaneous Classes: Dave Carns (IET)-Survey Class, Brian Goeltzenleuchter, Shari Stoddard, Amy Mumma World Wine Program, 2006- (Box-folder 45-11)
- Amber Joy Neystedt, 2005- (Box-folder 45-12)
- Linda Clark Santos, Liahnna Armstrong, 2005- (Box-folder 45-13)
- Development Staff: Mark Anderson, Paul Baker, Julia Cloninger, George Cole, Lauren Fortune, 2005- (Box-folder 45-14)
- Fall People: James Cook with Students (Studio), Michael Ervin (outdoor Portrait), Sanford Kinzer Trustee (Portrait), Alexander Lafollett (Classroom), Danielle Martinez (studio), Vijay Singh Studio Light Portrait, Jefferey Snedeker portrait with horn, 2005- (Box-folder 45-15)
- Fall CWU Stock Back Up, SUB/REC, 2005- (Box-folder 45-16)
- I.T. Development Day: Bob Perkins and Students Teaching Staff, 2005- (Box-folder 45-17)
- Heidi Szpeck Teaching, 2005- (Box-folder 45-18)
- Occupational Safety and Health Students with Fire department: Chlorine Drill hazmat, 2005- (Box-folder 45-19)
- Judith Kleck Teaching, 2005- (Box-folder 45-20)
- Brother 2 Brother Ken Denman COB Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-21)
- Brother 2 Brother Ken Denman COB Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-22)
- Miscellaneous: 04/2005 Naomi Wolfe, Vid CMER/Edit-Conceptual Shots, Bookstore Gift Shot Disc 2 (Box-folder 45-23)
- Peter Yarrow (Peter, Paul and Mary) Music Hall, 2005- (Box-folder 45-24)
- Mark Polishook, Leslie Webb, 2005- (Box-folder 45-25)
- Summer Campus Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-26)
- Summer Campus Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-27)
- Bolcom and Morris, no date- (Box-folder 45-28)
- Garison Keillor Shot, no date- (Box-folder 45-29)
- Chris S. New Sub Rec Opening, 2006- (Box-folder 45-30)
- Orientation Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 45-31)
- Orientation Disc 5, 2005- (Box-folder 45-32)
- Orientation Disc 6, 2005- (Box-folder 45-33)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-34)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-35)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 45-36)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 45-37)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 5, 2005- (Box-folder 45-38)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 7, 2005- (Box-folder 45-39)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 8, 2005- (Box-folder 45-40)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 9, 2005- (Box-folder 45-41)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 10, 2005- (Box-folder 45-42)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 11, 2005- (Box-folder 45-43)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 12, 2005- (Box-folder 45-44)
- Headshots: Admin, Trustees, Theater Arts Faculty, 2005- (Box-folder 45-45)
- 4th of July fireworks, Deccio Art, 2005- (Box-folder 45-46)
- President's report: McIntyre with Students, Pickett/Takahashi, Podium, Report Finals, RCA Microphone, Chris Schedler, Tortilla Curtain, 2005- (Box-folder 45-47)
- Moses Lake Interiors, 2005- (Box-folder 45-48)
- SUB/REC Courts, SS conceptual, Valley Sun Break (Dawn), 2005- (Box-folder 45-49)
- Darwin Day Shots Soltz/Bellah, Studio Concept Shots for President's Report, 2005- (Box-folder 45-50)
- Conceptual Water Shots, 2005- (Box-folder 45-51)
- Orientation Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 45-52)
- Student Volunteers at Senior Center, 2005- (Box-folder 45-53)
- Electrical Engineering Technology, Occupational Safety and Health, Students, 2005- (Box-folder 45-54)
- Industrial Engineering Technology Students, machine Shop with Bill Cattin, 2005- (Box-folder 45-55)
- IET Finals C.MGT/OSH, EET/MET, 2005- (Box-folder 45-56)
- Homecoming: Brandy Carlile, Robert Kennedy, Día De Los Muertos, Homecoming Dances Band in the SURC pit, Alumni Awards Banquet, Excellence in Teaching Awards, Class of '56 Reunion, Football/Rugby, Fans and Band, 2006- (Box-folder 45-57)
- Homecoming: Kennedy Banquet, Día de Los Muertos Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-58)
- Homecoming: Kennedy Banquet, SURC Grand Opening Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 45-59)
- Homecoming: Kennedy, Excellence in Teaching Banquet Disc 5, 2006- (Box-folder 45-60)
- Commencement DVD, 2006- (Box-folder 45-61)
- Commencement Convocation, Both E. Side, Westside, 2006- (Box-folder 45-62)
- Miscellaneous: 2006 Percussion, Classroom Shots, Discover Picks 2005, Envelope shot; Fabry, Levente Chemo Shot with Grad Student, KNDO at FA Office, Habitat 01/2006 Concept Shots Seattle Columbia Tower, Twilight Satellite Shots (Box-folder 45-63)
- Mariners Alumni Event Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-64)
- Mariners Alumni Events Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-65)
- Studio Water Shots, 2006- (Box-folder 45-66)
- President's Report Images, Accept Book Images, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 45-67)
- Habitat: Barto Package Gals, Alicia Blaine, Muzzall graphics, Stacey Klippenstein and Rich DeShields, James Wagner, 2006- (Box-folder 45-68)
- Habitat: Chicks on T.V., Central Transit, Jennifer Estroff, Fisheye hall shots, RHC walking and Hanging Out, 2006- (Box-folder 45-69)
- President's Report Photos Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-70)
- President's Report Photos Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-71)
- President's Report Photos Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 45-72)
- President's Report Images, 2006- (Box-folder 45-73)
- President's Report Pieces, 2006- (Box-folder 45-74)
- SUB REC Top-off, 2005- (Box-folder 45-75)
- Extreme Line Waiting, 2005- (Box-folder 45-76)
- Moses Lake Ribbon Cut, CWU Percussion Ensemble, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 45-77)
- Yakima River Clean Up Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-78)
- Yakima River Clean Up Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-79)
- Miscellaneous: AFROTC Cadets/Barge, 2005 Student Commencement Speakers, Habitat for Humanity Student Volunteer, Library Book Mark Design Winners, Memorial Day Service (Box-folder 45-80)
- Foreign Language Day (Visiting high school kids) Henna/Chinese Calligraphy, African Present/Dance, 2005- (Box-folder 45-81)
- Foreign Language Day (visiting high school kids) Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-82)
- Miscellaneous McConnel Spot, 2005 CAMP group, Recycle Concept Shots, Suitcase Disc 2, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 45-83)
- Moses Lake Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-84)
- Moses Lake Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-85)
- Orientation Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-86)
- Orientation Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 45-87)
- Orientation Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 45-88)
- Mammoth Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-89)
- Mammoth Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-90)
- Mammoth Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 45-91)
- President's Report Tony Aronica, Athlete Trio Portrait, Tim Burnham, C.O.B. Code of Ethics, Project C.R.O.A.K., Diversity Portrait, Macro EYE Shots, Fishbowl Study, Gear up, Compass Shots Hoskins/Menke, HPV Crew, Lombard Hall, Lubinski, Map Shots, Alma McConnell Project C.A.T. Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 45-92)
- President's Report: McIntyre with Students, Pickett/Takahashi, Podium and Seal, Report Finals, RCA Microphone, Chris Schedler, Tortilla Curtain, 2005- (Box-folder 45-93)
- Music Building, Art Glass, 2005- (Box-folder 45-94)
- Dave Carns-Survey Class, Mumma -World Wine Class, Orchesis Dance with McConnell, 2006- (Box-folder 45-95)
- Dinning Cinco De Mayo, 2005- (Box-folder 45-96)
- Students Playing Friendly Game of Basketball with Music Building in Background, 2005- (Box-folder 45-97)
- Residence Life Images, 2005- (Box-folder 45-98)
- Rez Life Images for Susan, 2005- (Box-folder 45-99)
- Presidents Report Images: 2004 Pacurh Award, Alumni Donors, Robert Carbaugh, Des Portes K., Alex Lafolett-Scenics, Architecture, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 45-100)
- President's Report Tony Aronica, Athlete Trio Portrait, Tim Burnham, C.O.B. Code of Ethics, Project C.R.O.A.K., Diversity Portrait, Macro EYE Shots, Fishbowl Study, Gear up, Compass Shots Hoskins/Menke, HPV Crew, Lombard Hall, Lubinski, Map Shots, Alma McConnell Project C.A.T. Disc 1 2nd copy, 2005- (Box-folder 45-101)
- Central Today: Aja/Talon, Wendy Bohson, Gene Brain, Amy Castner, Linda Graf, Rep. Dunn, Merwin, Tim Melbourne, Steve Nourse, Santos/Street/Spzek Leaf play images, 2005- (Box-folder 45-102)
- Media Services Staff Shots: Chinn Covey Douglas, Newman, O'Brien, Shapiro, Smart, Spencer, Whitaker, 2005- (Box-folder 45-103)
- COB Marketing Club Guest Speaker: Sandy Wheeler, 2005- (Box-folder 45-104)
- Stock Photos: mark Goodenberger Sura Rath, Liuxi Meng, 2004 Central Today, Mike Reilly (Box-folder 45-105)
- Miscellaneous: Carol Mausley-Braun, Mike Milligan Tech 3rd grade class, VP of Student Affairs Charlotte Tullos-Group Staff, Big Check with Mike Smith, 2005- (Box-folder 45-106)
- Jerilyn McIntyre: Portrait in Garden, 2005- (Box-folder 45-107)
- Jen Estroff, 2005- (Box-folder 45-108)
- Melissa Shots: Boogie Cats, International BBQ, NT BBQ Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 4-109)
- Melissa Shots: NT BBQ, Central Washington Fair Mammoth Display, 2006- (Box-folder 45-110)
- Rafting, 2007- (Box-folder 45-111)
- Wenatchee Art Dedication and Wine Event, 2007- (Box-folder 45-112)
- CAH Miscellaneous: chieftains, Moawad Jazz Invitational, Orchesis Rehearsal, Theater Arts Classes, 2006- (Box-folder 45-113)
- Homecoming: Excellence in Teaching Banquet, Band in Stands, Fans in Stands, 2006- (Box-folder 45-114)
- Barge, Michaelson, P.E., 2006- (Box-folder 45-115)
- Dean, Hogue, Samuelson, 2006- (Box-folder 45-116)
- CWU Monkey Photo, 2006- (Box-folder 45-117)
- Campus Lens Baby Shots Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-118)
- Campus Lens Baby Shots Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-119)
- One book One Campus Stack, 2006- (Box-folder 45-120)
- Espresso Concept Shots, no date- (Box-folder 45-121)
- SURC dining Signage conceptual Shots, no date- (Box-folder 45-122)
- COB Dean's Council Breakfast and Portrait, 2007- (Box-folder 45-123)
- David Wain-Coon Event, 2007- (Box-folder 45-124)
- Summer Session Kickoff-Volleyball in Front of SURC, Surfing, 2007- (Box-folder 45-125)
- Nate Slover Shots Campus/Students, N.T. Carnival, 2007- (Box-folder 45-126)
- Alumni Art, Exhibit-P.S.D Finals, 2007- (Box-folder 45-127)
- Rez Life and Survival Guide, 2007- (Box-folder 45-128)
- President's Report, Book Stack, Case Award, Holga Tests, Comp/ Email Photos, Campaign Materials11/2007 Acceptance Book: Dining Employees, Excited CWU Fans Campus/Mall Shots, Miscellaneous Students (Box-folder 45-129)
- Holmes X-mas Dinner, President X-mas Reception, 2007- (Box-folder 45-130)
- Studio Cello Shots, 2007- (Box-folder 45-131)
- Case Statements Images, 2007- (Box-folder 45-132)
- Bite of the Burg Nate Slover Pics, 2007- (Box-folder 45-133)
- CWU Student Health, Counseling and Wellness Center, 2007- (Box-folder 45-134)
- Kids Rock! Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-135)
- Kids Rock! Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-136)
- Kids Rock! Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 45-137)
- Wenatchee Center Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-138)
- Wenatchee Center Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-139)
- Wenatchee Center Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 45-140)
- Wenatchee Center Disc 4, 2006- (Box-folder 45-141)
- Commencement Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-142)
- Commencement Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 45-143)
- Commencement Disc 3, 2007- (Box-folder 45-144)
- Commencement Disc 4, 2007- (Box-folder 45-145)
- Commencement Disc 5, 2007- (Box-folder 45-146)
- Commencement Disc 6, 2007- (Box-folder 45-147)
- Commencement Disc 7, 2007- (Box-folder 45-148)
- Commencement Disc 8, 2007- (Box-folder 45-149)
- Commencement Disc 9, 2007- (Box-folder 45-150)
- Commencement Disc 12, 2007- (Box-folder 45-151)
- Commencement Disc 13, 2007- (Box-folder 45-152)
- Commencement Disc 14, 2007- (Box-folder 45-153)
- Commencement Disc 15, 2007- (Box-folder 45-154)
- Commencement Disc 16, 2007- (Box-folder 45-155)
- Commencement Disc 17, 2007- (Box-folder 45-156)
- Commencement Disc 18, 2007- (Box-folder 45-157)
- Homecoming SURC Grand Opening Event Disc 4, 2006- (Box-folder 45-158)
- Homecoming SURC Alumni Awards Banquet Disc 12, 2006- (Box-folder 45-159)
- Hebeler Relief Sculpture, 2006- (Box-folder 45-160)
- Christmas Reception, 2007- (Box-folder 45-161)
- Orientation Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-162)
- Central connections: 2006 convocation Speaker, The Adelines at Homecoming 2006 Game, Ozden Bayazit, Basketball/Soccer, Beau Baldwin Press Conference, 40's Aviation Cadets Image, circuit Board Conceptual, Ellwood, manor, Faculty Books, President in Hawaii; Hummell, Katie; McIrvin, Meagan; McIntyre SURC Portrait, "One Book" Shots, Stevenson's at Montel Show; Nielson, Tod; Wilson, Dale, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 45-163)
- Central Connections: Athletic Hall of Fame Banquet- Baldwin, B., Building Bridges, Cordner, D.; Den Boer, L.; Hummel, K.; Mattis; Nygard, A.; Street Signs/letters Thomas, C.; Backlund,P. hiking shots-Taneum, D. Coffman, 2007- (Box-folder 45-164)
- Beacon Kairos Lyceum Rez Life, 2007- (Box-folder 45-165)
- Garrison Keillor, 05/2006 Blocom and Morris Photos by Chris Sheats (Box-folder 45-166)
- Masquerade African Story Tellers in the SURC Pit, 2006- (Box-folder 45-167)
- Bite of the Burg, Blade Signing, 2006- (Box-folder 45-168)
- Discover Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-169)
- Discover Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-170)
- Homecoming: Football Crowd, Players, Cheerleaders, Marching Band Disc 7, 2006- (Box-folder 45-171)
- Homecoming: Band, Rugby, Homecoming Parade, Some Fan Shots Disc 8, 2006- (Box-folder 45-172)
- Homecoming: Football Game, Rugby Game Match Disc 9, 2006- (Box-folder 45-173)
- Homecoming: Rugby Game, Alumni Awards, Football Game Disc 10, 2006- (Box-folder 45-174)
- Homecoming: Alumni Awards Banquet Disc 11, 2006- (Box-folder 45-175)
- E.S.L. Rafting, 2006- (Box-folder 45-176)
- E.S.L. Rafting Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-177)
- Fall Students Leaves/ SURC Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-178)
- Fall Students Leaves/ SURC Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-179)
- Winter Campus snow Shoeing, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 45-180)
- President's Office Gift Portrait, Kamola Icicles, Fireside Chat, Melissa Hogrefe Shots, 2006- (Box-folder 45-181)
- Brother to Brother Christine Day, 2006- (Box-folder 45-182)
- Fall Color by Nate Slover, Hebeler Stair by Rich Villacres, no date- (Box-folder 45-183)
- Ellensburg Rodeo Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-184)
- Ellensburg Rodeo Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 45-185)
- Career Quest Spring Orientation, Welcome East SURC Patio, Virginia Tech Forum at the SURC, 2007- (Box-folder 45-186)
- Crimson and Black Gala, 2007- (Box-folder 45-187)
- Deep Sea Daze, Massive Monkees, 2007- (Box-folder 45-188)
- Central Transit, 2007- (Box-folder 45-189)
- Building Bridges, 2007- (Box-folder 45-190)
- Moawad Jazz invite, 2007- (Box-folder 45-191)
- Wenatchee Art, Dedication and Wine Event, 2007- (Box-folder 45-192)
- Beacon: COB Dean's Council Meeting, 03/2006 Federal Reserve Team Meeting, Professor Christopher Lee at Des Moines Center, Mark Pearson Port, Christine Day Brother to Brother, Regina Graw-Crockett, Shaw Conceptual Shots, Building Bridges Event DVD (Box-folder 45-193)
- Desktop Back Up, CWU Stock, Headshots, 2006- (Box-folder 45-194)
- Discover Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-195)
- Holiday Extravaganza Photos by Melissa Hogreffe, 2006- (Box-folder 45-196)
- Fall Mt. Stuart Health Fair, Seattle Symphony, Winter Fest, Second City, Washington State Supreme Court Judges photos by Melissa Hogreffe, 2006- (Box-folder 45-197)
- COB Dean's Council, 2006- (Box-folder 45-198)
- Miscellaneous barge with Flags ( All three), Cabinet Portrait, Cabinet Portrait, clue Tools (Studio), Music Night Shot (fireworks light), SURC Stock, 2006- (Box-folder 45-199)
- Christmas Reception Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-200)
- Timothy Dittnuer, 2006- (Box-folder 45-201)
- Spring Miscellaneous- 06/2006 Central Connections Images, Makiko Doi/Japanese Calligraphy, Football Captain Shot/ coach Z, Flight Tech Airport MGR scholarship, Garden Shots, Gear Up, Mike McGavick Forum, 2006 Retiree Portraits, Theatre Arts Faculty Portraits, Rufus Woods Papers (Box-folder 45-202)
- Distinguished Professors Bowers, Nethery, Lewis, 2006- (Box-folder 45-203)
- Maya Chachava Painting Studio, 2006- (Box-folder 45-204)
- Miscellaneous People: Tony Aronica, Jeffery Dippman, Jason Knirck, Governor Gregoire, 2006- (Box-folder 45-205)
- Miscellaneous People: 2006 Conference Group on McConnell, Rebecca bowers, Cabinet Group Portrait, John Drinkwater, Kids in Fountain, 2003 Debbie Prigge (Box-folder 45-206)
- R.A. Group Shots Disc 1, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 45-207)
- Wenatchee Center Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-208)
- Wenatchee Center Grand Opening Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-209)
- Working Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 45-210)
- Mammoth Dig Disc 6, no date- (Box-folder 45-211)
- Yakima River Clean up shots by Melissa Hogrefe, 2006- (Box-folder 45-212)
- Bite of the Burg Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-213)
- Bite of the Burg Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-214)
- Wenatchee Center Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-215)
- Students Throwing Snow/Snowman Interview, 2007- (Box-folder 45-216)
- COB Dean's council Breakfast, 2006 Beacon Ed/Jennifer Phillips, Ruong Lou (Box-folder 45-217)
- Des Moines Pierce, Patricia Daniels, Key Sun, Mary Pack, Pierce Students, Des Moines/ Pierce Exteriors, 2007- (Box-folder 45-218)
- Orientation Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 45-219)
- Move-In Wildcat Cup, 2007- (Box-folder 45-220)
- Source, 2007- (Box-folder 45-221)
- Higher Ed Day in Olympia, 2007- (Box-folder 45-222)
- Solar Dragster and Crew, Step Science Students in Lab, Becky Watson Marketing Class, 2007- (Box-folder 45-223)
- Dining Employees, Rez Hall Rooms, 2007- (Box-folder 45-224)
- Wild About Reading Shots Wenatchee Center, Architecture Shots, no date- (Box-folder 45-225)
- Move-In Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-226)
- Move-In Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-227)
- Bite of the Burg, 2007- (Box-folder 45-228)
- Rock Wall, 2007- (Box-folder 45-229)
- Fall Campus Disc 3, 2007- (Box-folder 45-230)
- Fun Student Shots, 2007- (Box-folder 45-231)
- Wellington's Wildfire, 2007- (Box-folder 45-232)
- Good Totem Shots, 2007- (Box-folder 45-233)
- Library Totem, Bouillon Hall, 2007- (Box-folder 45-234)
- R.A. Group Shots Disc 2, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 45-235)
- RA Groups, Pres Speaker L and W Faculty Group of 4 Kleck, Powell, Whitcomb, Kramer Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 45-236)
- Miscellaneous People C.A.M.P. Group, Stephanie Drotz, Barbara Hodges, Sirrine, D.;Tenney, D.; Tormey, R., 2006- (Box-folder 45-237)
- Miscellaneous People Kristen Bates, CWU Credit Union, Stephanie Drotz, Brandon Kennedy, 2006- (Box-folder 45-238)
- Chenyang Li, Nancy Worden, Michael Ogden in TV Production Room With Students, International Week Food Sampling, 2006- (Box-folder 45-239)
- Hoover, A.; Maul, A., 2006- (Box-folder 45-240)
- Wenatchee Center, 2006- (Box-folder 45-241)
- Wenatchee Center Grand Opening Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 45-242)
- Miscellaneous Studio Portraits-Basketball Coaches, Jonathan Gordon, Jesse Days, Sandy Perline, Patt Notter, Ken Young, 2006- (Box-folder 45-243)
- Secilia Garcia, Karen Blair, Larry Gookin, 2006- (Box-folder 45-244)
- The Macinko's Studio Book Shot, 2006- (Box-folder 45-245)
- Portraits-The Howard's, Chris Sheats, Rich Villacres, 2006- (Box-folder 45-246)
- Jazz Recital, 2006- (Box-folder 45-247)
- CWU Comp/Back Up, 2006- (Box-folder 45-248)
- Miscellaneous- Chachava Teaching (Painting), Christine Day, Donna Stack teaching (Sculpture), Kid's Arbor Day Event, Garrison, Keilor, 2006- (Box-folder 45-249)
- Charles Li, Gnanarajah, R.; Willisford, R., 2006- (Box-folder 45-250)
- CWU Distance Professors 1-8X10 Each, no date- (Box-folder 45-251)
- CWU Distance Professors 8X10's Batch 2, no date- (Box-folder 45-252)
- Accept Book, 01/2006 Beacon, Development Portraits, Andy Piacsek, Recreation Center Grand Open, Donna Stack, 11/2005 SUB REC Entry, Whitcomb/McKamey, www 2005 Picks, 01/2006 Ext. Line Waiting (Box-folder 45-253)
- Miscellaneous- Civic Engagement Interns/Portraits, Construction Career Fair, SUB Rec Sports, 2006- (Box-folder 45-254)
- Miscellaneous-2006 Accept Book, 01/2006 Beacon, Development Crew, Andy Piacsek, Recreation Center Grand Open, Donna Stack, 11/2005 Sub Rec Entry, Whitcomb/McKamey, WWW 2005, EXT. Line Waiting 01/2006 (Box-folder 45-255)
- Career Quest, 04/2006 Orchesis, 2006 Spike Arlt Track Meet (Box-folder 45-256)
- Spring Miscellaneous- Athletic Hall of Fame Dinner, Butterfly Garden Dedication-Mt Stuart Wichterman Kinder Class with Butterflies, East Side Student Communication Speakers, Jazz Band in SURC Pit, Student Appreciaton Day, Wildcat Madness, 2006- (Box-folder 45-257)
- Legacy Builders Lunch, 2006- (Box-folder 45-258)
- Schaake's, 10/2006 Judy Shepard (Box-folder 45-259)
- Fall- Boo Central, Brandi Carlile, Fall Campus, Hoop Dance, Homecoming Dances, Melissa Hogrefe Photos, 2006- (Box-folder 45-260)
- Ware Fair, 2006- (Box-folder 45-261)
- Christmas Reception Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 45-262)
- CWU Students Circle, 2007- (Box-folder 45-263)
- Vocal Jazz One Rehearsal Vijay Singh, 2007- (Box-folder 45-264)
- Papss Unveiling, Bobby Mcferrin, 2007- (Box-folder 45-265)
- Science Building, Bomb Threat, Free Speech Festival, Senior Alumni Banquet, 2007- (Box-folder 45-266)
- Foreign Language Day, 2007- (Box-folder 45-267)
- AHOF, 2007- (Box-folder 45-268)
- Studio Mace Shots, 2007- (Box-folder 45-269)
- Spring Campus, 2007- (Box-folder 45-270)
- Summer Campus Stock, Lens Baby Shots, 2007- (Box-folder 45-271)
- Orientation Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 45-272)
- CWU Pennants, 2007- (Box-folder 45-273)
- Fisheye Language and Literature/Mall Shots, 5007- (Box-folder 45-274)
- SAEM Retreat Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-275)
- SAEM Retreat Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 45-276)
- Cascade Land Conservancy Awards Lunch, 2007- (Box-folder 45-277)
- Fall Campus Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-278)
- Duncan Naming Events, 2007- (Box-folder 45-279)
- Fall Color Campus, Yakima River Clean Up Shots by Nate Slover, 2007- (Box-folder 45-280)
- Nate Slover's Fall Shots Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-281)
- Nate Slover's Fall Shots Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 45-282)
- Central Transit Yellow Leaves, 2007- (Box-folder 45-283)
- COB New Majors Party, Computer Science Students, 2007- (Box-folder 45-284)
- CWU Die Shots (Embossing), 2007- (Box-folder 45-285)
- Nate Slover Shots-Bouldering Competition, Student Torso's Walking, Football Game, Job Fair, Leaf Shots, Pep Rally, Washoe Memorial, Snowman and Students, Photo Student with Light Table, 2007- (Box-folder 45-286)
- Percussion Concert Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-287)
- Percussion Concert Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 45-288)
- Percussion Concert Disc 3, 2007- (Box-folder 45-289)
- Orientation Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 45-290)
- Commencement Disc 10, 2007- (Box-folder 45-291)
- #1-#45, 2003- (Box-folder 46-1)
- #47 (Box-folder 46-2)
- #49-50, 2004- (Box-folder 46-3)
- 1991-1992 Calendar, 10/28/1992 Back Up (Box-folder 46-4)
- Centennial Memories Section 3, no date- (Box-folder 46-5)
- Centennial Scans, no date- (Box-folder 46-6)
- Newsletters, Fluffy-Summer, no date- (Box-folder 46-7)
- Deep Sea Poster, no date- (Box-folder 46-8)
- Mike's Borders and Mike's Globe Illustration, no date- (Box-folder 46-9)
- O'Hara, Letterhead/Strategic Plan, no date- (Box-folder 46-10)
- 5 Year Plan-Jobs-Memos Disk 2, no date- (Box-folder 46-11)
- Apprentice Advertising, CWU Auxiliary Services Advertising and Publications and Calendar August and July, no date- (Box-folder 46-12)
- Centennial Memories Section 2 Back Up, no date- (Box-folder 46-13)
- Centennial Memories Section 1, no date- (Box-folder 46-14)